Here we go... Aust TV has begun.
Yay!
Nice to meet you!
Nice to meet you. I'm from Aichi Prefecture.
I'm from Aichi Prefecture, and I'm a fourth term student of Hinata-zaka 46.
I'm Haruka Yamashita, the new announcer of Aust TV.
And I'll be working with a popular influencer and social networking commentator
Popular influencer and SNS commentator
Momo-san Wakabayashi!
Pleased to meet you.
I bit it right away.
It's totally fine.
This show is about Nagoya as a cultural center.
Nagoya's culture hub, and the next generation of Aust.
Mr. Stretchy's, a Wakata Geisha, and Mr. Manju Dai-teikoku
and Manju Taiteikoku, who are the next generation of Nagoya's
We'll be reporting on all of them!
Thank you very much!
By the way, Haruka-chan is called Haruharu
Haruka-chan is called Haruharu by everyone.
I don't mean to be presumptuous, but...
I'm a little embarrassed, but is it okay if I call you Haruharu-chan today?
I'd be very happy if you could call me Haruharu-chan.
Thank you very much.
Beautiful angel... it's like looking at a chick.
I'll go with "Chick Girl" then.
I'm looking forward to it.
I don't know what you're talking about, Geisha Wakata.I don't know what to say about you, Geisha Wakata.
Do you like Momochan?
Do you like her? Is it okay if I call you Momochan?
Can I call you Momochan?
Yes, please.
Momo-chan, please.
What is this?
It looks like someone is watching the video.
Please call me Haruharu, Momochan.
I'm from Aichi Prefecture.
I used to come to Osu when I was a student.
Mr. Wakata Geisha
Oh, Momochan is...
Momochan-san
Cute.
Have you ever been to Osu, Momochan?
I've only been once, but I don't remember much.
Is there a shopping street with restaurants?
Yes, there are a lot of them.
Please tell us about the charm of Osu.
Yes, I've been there a lot.
I went to Osu when I was a college student.
I think I can tell you a lot about the charms of Osu.
I think so.
I think, I will do my best.
We'll be filming on location, too.
I'm really looking forward to it!
Let's report Osu thoroughly!Let's do a thorough report on Osu!
Let's go!
Haruharu, you've got a good view!
Now, from here, I'll introduce the highlights of the show.
Oosu TV will bring you the charm of Oosu, the cultural center of Nagoya!
K-pro, a comedy live show organizer, is planning a Nagoya-only unit from Nagoya.
Stretchies and Manju Dai-teikoku will appear!
The two groups of young comedians who will lead the next generation will thoroughly investigate Oos.
Also joining us to support the show are Hisashi and Selina.
They won the right to appear on the show by auditioning for the live-streaming site Showroom.
I, Nico Imaha, who does the narration for this show, was also selected through an audition.
Please check out our live streaming showroom.
You will surely want to go to Aus!
Opening of Aus TV
Introducing the charms of Aus, the cultural center of Nagoya!
We'll introduce you to some of the best spots in Aust.
First of all, we'll be filming on location with Mr. Stretchy's!
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you. I'm Stretchies.
Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you too.
Thank you very much.
A beautiful woman two meters high.
I've got an uncle like that.
Do you have any tricks to make him double?
A winning strategy? A surefire way to win?
Hissatsu?
I'm like a deadly workman.I'm like a deadly workman.
Do you have a winning formula?
Well, we'd like to double our challenge by filming the Aussie gourmet.
We'd like to double our challenge by shooting a gourmet meal in Aus.
Gourmet food is relatively easy.
I'm sure it will be easy, so I'm looking forward to it.
What? That's great.
First of all, I'd like to challenge
Stretchy's, a highly educated comedian who graduated from Keio University.
Stretchies are expected to be the next breakout comedian.
They are expected to be the next breakout comedians!
First, the four came to Rockin' Robin, a restaurant where you can enjoy authentic hamburgers!
The small and cute hamburgers are sure to be a photo op!
This one looks so good, it's easy to take a picture of it.
No matter how you take the picture, if you don't take a picture of this
If it doesn't look good
If it doesn't look good, just take a picture of this and it will look good.
As long as you take a picture of this, it'll be fine.
I wonder if I can take this picture.
Fukushima-san looks a little anxious.
What do you think? This is not so good.
It's pretty good.
It's not so bad.
I thought it would be worse.
The angle of view is right in the middle, so it's pretty good.
Next is a collaboration between an idol and a hamburger!
Cute!
Amazing!Oh, my God.
Come here with your meal ticket.
I'm serious.
You know, I can see why you're such a fan of this.
He's so cute.
Oh, my God.
There's a lot of tickets.
That's a lot of pictures.
They're so cute!
They're really cute.
This is so cute!
It's so cute!
Oh, my God.
I don't know what I'm going to do now that I've taken all these pictures.
This is so modern.
It looks like something a modern girl would do.
I should have measured the angle of view a little higher.
I see.
It's a little too close.
It's not too bad for a first time.
The riff is a little bit... without the help of Haruharu.
I have feelings about that.
That's true.
Shall we move on?
Yes, sir.
The two Stretchies who made the hamburgers look good
We're going to take a stroll through the streets of Ozu in search of even more impressions.I'm going to explore the town of Ozu in search of more reflections.
Then I'm in the mood for something sweet next time.
That's for sure.
It was salty earlier.
I want some.
Do you have any recommendations, Haruharu?
If you walk around here, I'm sure you'll find something.
There are a lot of stores.
That's right.
Look at this greedy guy on the left.
Greedy!
What I found here is a store specializing in black fulls.
There are many cute photo spots in the store, and it's popular among Generation Z.
The inside of the store is also very Korean.
It's a cafe!
I was recently in Korea until yesterday, and there were a lot of cafes like this one.
Maybe this kind of thing is popular. It's like 2 dimensional.
Korea is a parfait store like this.
On the contrary.
The oaths, the pillars...
You're probably right.
It's the most advanced osa.
They're doing it right here.
Well, let's start with the mangrove.
That's great.
This is the moment.
I'm so excited.Exciting!
I will narrow it down for you.
please?
Oh great!
That's so good, that's so good, that's so good!
Oh my goodness, oh my goodness, oh my goodness!
Oh, my God, you've narrowed it down so much.
I'm sure there is.
I'm sorry.
They're ignoring everything!
What is it?
This one has the sweet smell of clear sweet potatoes.
I see.
The aroma is amazing.
They're putting in the smell.
It's like a little smoke when you open it.
It smokes when you open it.
This handbasket.
Here we go.
Oh, wow.
That's great.
You know, that's not what I'm talking about anymore.
This is the main one.
There it is.
It's a Moropahe!
Delicious!
They put so much on it!You put so much on it.
That's great.
It's personal.
Don't let him send you to this school.
Come on. If you're at the loading dock, Haruharu's there too.
Haruharu's posing, too.
No, no, no, no...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, you're really getting it.
No, no, no... it's not two or two
Oh, man...
It's so good! Please!
Please!
This is strawberry soft serve.
Wow, great!
The ice cream melts in seconds, so bite the bullet.
Bite hard, bite early.
This one right here. Oh, it's so cute!
So cute!
That's so good! That's so good!
You're good.
You have good taste.
It's cute.
It's really not good.
You have a real sense of style.
It's really good.
You should do a lot of instagrams.
But if there's a mirror here...But the fact that there's a mirror here...
I think everyone is probably taking pictures of each other through the mirror.
Cute.
Funny.
You're not looking very appealing.
Stretchy's took Momochan's advice and took a picture of the girls in harmony.
After the photo shoot, it's time for the long-awaited tasting!
Looks delicious!
Bon appétit!
Yum, it's delicious!
But this is not the croquel part yet!
LOL!
The ice cream is good, too.
It's good, but the croquel.
I mean, croqueles are kind of like a meal together.
It's difficult.
Mockingjay. Mockingjay.
Cute.
Delicious.
Croissant.
The crunch of a croissant and the stickiness of a waffle.
and the stickiness of a waffle at the same time.
and waffle at the same time.
A new taste sensation
It's a croissant!
Very good report!
Great, great, great report.
Okay, I want to go next.Then I want to go next.
It's big.
Oh, yummy.
Cute. Mockingjay. Mockingjay.
I'm squeezing the Mont Blanc.
It's got a really nice texture.
It's so good.
It's delicious.
Delicious.
That's why
I was able to shoot it twice.
It was delicious and
It was delicious.
It was great.
[ED].
Ozu is full of fun places.
But I've only been here once before.
Last time and this time too, it was really crowded.
There are so many different stores, it's really fun.
It's nice. There are so many bio-spots.
It's great!
That's great.
Let's take pictures!
I want to take a picture, I want to take a picture!
I want to take a picture.
He's so cute.
Nice, nice, nice.Good, good, good.
Delicious.
Looks good.
Yum. Yum.
It's okay. It's okay.
Is it okay?
It was delicious.
I want to eat it again.
Let's go again.
I want to go back.
Let's go together.
Thank you very much.
Next up, we have Manju Taiteikoku, the 7th generation of student comic storytellers, and they're a hot duo right now.
And now, Manju Taiteikoku. Pleased to meet you.
I'm so happy to meet you. What's your strategy?
Our strategy is to go with fashion this time.
Fashion. Take some good-looking pictures.
But fashion is said to be the most popular content for video content right now.
First timer! Your face is so white! Are you okay?
I suddenly have a very white face, but I have a white face.
I'd like to propose fashions that go well with white faces.
I'm looking forward to it!
The Great Manju Empire has chosen rice and ice as the stage for their battle!
Japan's largest reuse department store with a wide range of items from high-end to casual brands.
What are these?
They're earrings.
They're earrings?
That many?That many?
You have two of each.
That many?
Can you stop blurting it out?
If we start blabbing here.
I'm going to start acting like anyone's going to poke me.
That's a lot of food.
My eyes are watering.
You can have more ears than you know what to do with.
Ears, indeed.
They're amazing.
So wide.
They sparkle.
Kabachi.
What?
Kabachi?
I love it. It's fun.
I just went to a food location.
This one's more sparkling.
It was fun too, but...
It's okay.
Safe.
No problems.
It's hard to praise things.
They're all good, aren't they?
Each good
Wow!
Actually, I have something I'd like to show you today.In fact, I have an item I'd like to introduce today.
Graph.
It's a fad.
It's not trendy.
You'll be fine if you keep the graph.
Take a look at it.
Look at the price.
You'd better put it in glass.
It's always in there.
But today, I'd like to make a special offer.
1,380 yen.
If you're so inclined, please try it.
What?
Which finger is the right one to put it on?
Either finger is fine.
Which finger should I put it on?
Try it on your ring finger.
Actually, the ring finger.
I'd like to keep it for the future.
Idol.
I'm sorry, I'll put it on my thumb.
I'll go for the thumb.
Slowly, slowly, slowly...
You're so cute!
I'm sure I'm cute.
I'm sure.It's true.
This is who I want to marry.
I like this one and the one I'm going to marry.
I like this one for the translation finger.
Luxurious.
Wait a minute.
That's a line!
It's a line, isn't it?
That's great
Here.
She's so cute.
It's still rare to find a finger that matches the outfit.
What's this?
It's so heavy.
I can't move it.
You're right.
Momochan will take a picture with the graph of her dreams.
Sorry about this.
Hey...
What kind of boyfriend would give this to you?
I don't think so!
Haruharu and Momochan enjoying the luxury rings.
Next, we're going to take pictures in the men's dream watch corner.
Clock corner!
They sell watches too?
That's a little too much for a man.
Amazing!
The amount of watches is also amazing!The amount of watches is also amazing
And with the jewelry I mentioned earlier.
Cute.
You have to see it.
It's like ice blue.
It's so cute!
It's a watch.
I'd like you to try it on.
I was asking about the price.
Shall I put it on first?
First?
The ring finger, then.
I really like your ring finger.
I'll keep it. Ring finger.
Oh, wow.
It looks good, it looks good, it looks really good.
It looks good, it looks good, it looks good, it looks good.
It looks really good on you.
It looks good on you.
Very large in size
front and back
I knew it, but it's stylish
It's nice.
It's fashionable.
Let's take a picture!
This one...
I can't move this.
I can't move it.No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
I don't want to show it. I don't want to show it.
It doesn't show. It doesn't look good on you.
What time is it?
If it was my mouth, I'd put on airs.
I'm just trying to look cool.
That's what the bone said.
I'd be more cool if I said it with my mouth.
Oh, my God.
How much do you want?
Oh, sure.
Well, I'll tell you what... with the bones on.
Oh, my God.
Watch out, watch out, watch out.
Hold it right here.
You're stuck in a hole.
Oh, no.
We're over 1,000.
Yeah!
Oh, cool.
That's what they say.
How much is this?
The correct answer is...
20 million.
What?
It's me.
You're kidding!
20 million yen.20 million yen.
I'll take that.
Wow.
Wow! 20 million!
It looks great on you. It's absolutely ridiculous.
I still feel like 20 million. This is a gift for the viewers.
What kind of show has that much money?
Not this one, too.
The Manju Empire sold out with the power of money.
Now we'll make it sell at the tax-free corner.
Next, we're at the men's section!
Cute!
So cute!
It's so spacious!
I didn't know there was such a place.
So now that we're in the fashion area...
What is it?
There's only one thing to do.
What's that?
A fashion showdown!
Yay!
And we've decided on a theme.
If I were to go on a date with you, what would I wear?
What would you come dressed like?
The theme was fashion that girls would like.
say or do
Find outFind a
Dating
Find
GO
This ain't ET.
Oh no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no time!
Suddenly, a fashion showdown started.
The theme is "Which outfit would Momo-chan wear on a date?
What kind of outfits will they come up with?
That's her face. Isn't it nice?
The front?
I can't decide, I can't decide!
I like this one. Let's put this on top at the end.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, that's good.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no. Here.
It's hot. It's hot. It's okay.
It's okay, it's hot, it's okay.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Heh heh heh heh.
This is it. This is totally it.
This is it.
I see it.
I knew it! It's back. It's back.
This is good.
Let's do this. Okay.
I think it's okay.Is that okay?
Let's do this.
How confident are you?
Oh, my God.
It's perfect.
It's perfect. You can count on it.
Do you think...
Do you think she'll go on a date with you?
No, I think she's already gone.
I'd go on this one if I were you.
I don't see the point.
I don't know if I'd go.
I wonder how the two of them will coordinate with each other.
Now that you're all dressed, let's have them appear.
Please do.
Hi.
Hello.
What do you mean, they look a little bit alike?
Hi.
I'm completely dedicated to meeting people.
That's easy to understand.
I want to go on a date with you.
I want you to be able to find me easily.
I am.
What are you doing?
Hi. - Hi.
I'm Indiana Jones from Morse.
It's easier to see you from a distance if you're light years away.I can tell from a distance because it's brighter, so this
In the crowd.
I see.
But my dad likes red.
This one.
That's Rocky.
Maybe it's because his face is actually white and scary.
Still white.
I'm worried about him.
It's Christmas, Rocky.
It's really Christmas.
Christmas is the reddest day of the year.
Stop it.
It's fine.
I wonder which one she'll choose.
The one I want to go on a date with is Ecchan.
Yay!
My dad likes red.
Thanks, Dad.
Don't you like high school?
My dad doesn't dress like this.
My dad does racier anchors and stuff.
I don't think he'll make it.
I was hoping you'd pick something serious, though.
It's the reddest of the red.
I'm sure you two will go on a date with your real girlfriends.
Of course.
Of course, of course.Of course, of course.
I'm just trying to put something obvious on it.
The winner this time is Eccchan!
It's Eccchan!
Thank you very much.
How was your day touring around Austra-Macho?
Well, it was fun.
Really? It was great.
I've been here a lot, but there's still a lot I don't know.
Yes, it was.
No, really. Same here.
I don't know anything that can't be passed on forever.
Yeah, you made me laugh.
I still can't get that weight off of me.
I found it.
The weight of 20 million.
That's right.
You don't get to experience anything like this.
It's a lot of fun.
Now, let's see which one of us got the better picture of the duo.
I'll be the judge.
I knew it was more fun when I saw the diamonds.
Wait a minute.
Come on, come on.
That was a lot of fun.
That's how we do it, too.
It's getting to be a little less exciting for us when we're in the middle of painting the picture.
Don't say too much.Please don't say too much.
Here's a picture of what we're really thinking.
It's okay. We don't have to make an advanced war.
I like this one.
Peachy.
We have a mirror in the store.
You can actually use the mirror.
I see.
It's a mirror.
Here's the picture we chose.
Here it is.
Wow, that's not fair.
It's not fair.
That's not fair!
Haruharu.
You have one choice. The answer is...
You've got a great one on.
Now, let's hear your judgment, Momo.
The book I thought looked best this time
It's a picture of Haruharu wearing a ring.
No, no, no, no.
We have one too.
We have Haruharu's ring, too.
I've had a lot of Haruharu's.
It's the cuteness of Haruharu and the height of diamonds.
This one's a real miracle.
Yeah, we got an infinite number of shots.
Haruharu's Pitter Nuts.Pitter Nuts in Hallelujah
Infinite shot.
Wonderful.
Not a single photographic trick.
Just a little weak on top.
It was the one I shot crawling.
What should I do? The one I shot crawling.
spot win!
I see.
The clincher is that it's a spot win
There are still many more attractions in Oos
I'd like to convey them to you through this program.
Well then, I'll see you again!
Bye-bye!
Bye bye!
See you soon!